We'll call it order the amount of special utility authority board meeting for Monday, October 17th, 2022, and we'll have the invocation, my chief of the Mile 5 Department of Surgery, right?
Would you pray with me please?
God I thank you for this day, and I thank you for watching over each of us.
I pray God to be at this city and the people in it.
I ask you to be with the leaders and the decisions that they make.
Father, I thank you for your son, Jesus Christ.
It's in his name, I pray.
Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America and to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation under God, indivisible with liberty to us and so on.
Four public input on schedule personal appearances.
Five.
Consent agenda staff recommends we approve out of six and seven.
Eight.
Budget amendment number 23-08B.
MSUA admin purchase of Harvey's hair design property.
So this budget amendment is B.
You'll see a budget amendment A on your council meeting.
So when you have your MSUA hat on right now and this is contingent upon you approving with your council hat on on amendment A.
What this will do is this particular amendment accepts the money from the capital and permit fund and expends it for purchase of money.
Nine.
Gidel Stratten, Edmunds and Palmer.
Playing for GRDA, relaxing thing in the amount of $334.
what we've been doing on the last year.
The motion is to make a motion we're doing.
So, five, Williams, seven,
eight, four, four, three, four, four, four, four, four.
Hi.
Tim, award-least purchase and agreements to our best bank.
For payment of excavator, backhoe, wheel loader,
and two, SUV, four explorers, and give related signing.
And payment authority to the city manager, or his designated me.
So you have in your package a BA that lists all of those things.
You just talked about, not all of them are MSU-A.
A couple of them are for cities, so you'll see them on the next agenda.
But we did go out for financing proposals.
We got several.
I think this is in your packet, but I'm not sure.
But we got proposals from Arvest, Grand Lake, U.S. Bank, and Welch.
State bank, and the best financing numbers came back from Arvest
for all of the items.
And so it's my recommendation that you approve Arvest
to handle our least purchase agreements for those items.
We'll ask for three, five, seven, and ten year lease payment options.
And then the department heads, project managers, decided on the year,
based on what they have already been approved for, what they have in their budget for this year for this fiscal year.
And they all chose to make monthly payments as opposed to annual,
and you'll usually cost to a couple thousand dollars more.
I'm not good on the year.
I'm sorry, can you repeat that?
Why did Arvest not be on the 10 year option?
They didn't give a reason, they just wrote no bid.
Yeah, I mean, that's what I was looking for.
Yeah, no.
If I had to give you an answer, I would say it has to do with the value of the machinery at the end of that lease term.
One thing we've also asked our best degrees to do is to go ahead and start making our lease payments into an escrow count,
because it's such long lead times on some of these things are here now.
Some of these things are going to take a couple of years to get here.
So we would like to be in closer, as close as we can to pay off of those equipment, pieces of equipment when they actually get here.
And of course, if the equipment was to arrive and we weren't satisfied with it, that escrow count would just that will come back to us.
If we decided not to accept the equipment, that money would come back.
The wheel loader, the wheel loader is quite a ways out.
The excavator is here.
I think the backcoat can be here relatively quickly.
I don't know for certain the port explorers.
I know that they have some that have just arrived in that they are holding for us.
Those are police vehicles.
These two are not.
These two are one is community development.
And the other is code enforcement.
Yes.
I'm warm.
Is the excavator the one you had over at the port place?
No.
I was going to say we got a heck with the other.
What is it? What is it? What is it? Well, longer.
Please department or, yes.
Do we need that? Do we have to go forth?
First, I don't know if they are the identical explorers.
The police vehicles are utility vehicles and they're being,
what is the word. They're being outfitted.
They have to, which is going to take even longer.
So they've already been pushed into that process.
They're still not expected to be ready until mid-Dobembert December.
I need to be outfitted. Like the police department,
if they're not in my view.
Yes.
That's what she said they were.
I understand that.
But I understand that.
But what you said that they were actually four police cars,
the ones that they've already got over here.
Correct. The police, the police,
you'll see in the next, on the next, next month,
you'll see the police has three utilities.
They're not police farmers before they leave.
Okay. Okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Sorry.
When I was given that because if they're for the police
and we're already going to maybe get you some more,
then why would we do that?
No. No. I'm sorry. I probably did not articulate that very well.
I'm really not vehicle savvy.
I just want to get in and turn it on and go.
That's about it. Thank you.
I'll make a motion to approve.
Second.
Williams?
Senator?
Aye.
Thank you.
Crystal.
I'm sorry.
The award bid C22-32 for annual tree trimming.
The approval contract contingent upon the submission.
It required contract documents and approved city manager.
Or his designated need to sign.
Notice to proceed.
So if you notice in the packet,
we had three bitters.
We had Arco Mo.
Prochary and Aspun.
We are recommending Aspun.
Aspun is $5,000 more.
A little less than that for the whole year.
If he worked.
Every week of the year.
The reason we went with Aspun is they have a lot larger for prints.
Excuse me.
In the state.
In case we need to.
You know, first storms we've had, we had a small tornado, we had bacon on board, we had
four crews in at that time, as well as our overtime rate is cheaper.
You know, it's been, we reached out to both companies that had very close on prices, and so on
the responses from the emails included in the packet, Osborne has over 460 employees currently
working in the state of Oklahoma, the email for pro-tree shows they have 12 employees, but
six of them being previous tree-termers, and mine would be their only tree-terming contract.
So five to a little less than 5,000 for a full year.
So they're weekly total, this is if their whole crew worked 40 hours, I'm going to be $6,374
dollars versus $6,456 dollars, yes they're.
And I mean it is nice that we do, I mean we are, I hate to say it, but we are due to
having ice drums sometime and I mean, so, yeah, so, it's just nice to have the bigger
crews that choose from to bring in extra crews, is that Osborne, I think they do mostly, I
know they use, I know they do still what I don't know if they're still there or not.
Yeah, I'll make a motion to approve.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah.
12 other new business of any, which is the position of this agenda.
13 staff reports.
14 community trusty community announcements.
13 adjournments.